布莱恩: 所以我们要在这里做些什么
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
what we're gonna start doing here,
我们会开始从 API中读取实时数据
is we're actually gonna to start
reading live data from an API.
> > 布莱恩: 这会让我们感到兴奋，所以我们会看到宠物收养她。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Which is gonna be exciting,
so we're gonna see pets to adopt her.
所以这其实是从 Petfinder 来的
And so this is gonna actually come
from Petfinder which is like one of
找到宠物的最简单方法
the easiest ways to find pets to adopt.
所以如果你在这里看到的是你想要领养的
So if you see a patt here
use that you want to adopt,
你一定要这么做
you should definitely do it.
您在前端主斜杠宠物中所带的 Petfinder 客户机为
And the Petfinder client that you brought
in the front end master slash pet is
都已经被安排好了
already all set up to do that.
现在，我要展示如何处理 React 中的同步代码。
So I'm gonna show you now how to handle
a synchronous code inside of React.
>> 布莱恩: 好的，我要你先做，我刚才说的
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so what I want you to
do first, again I mentioned earlier
虽然你可以在这里放置不同的地方
that while you can put in different
locations up here, I actually have,
至少暂时限制在西雅图的西雅图和加利福尼亚州旧金山
at least temporarily, limited this to
Seattle, WA, and San Francisco, CA.
原因是我们有一个开发商钥匙我们不想让他们的 API
Reason being is that we have one developer
key and we don't wanna hammer their API,
所以我们才会把自己局限在几个
so that's why we're kind of limiting
ourselves to just a couple of
地理区域。
geographical areas.
如果我们能想出更好的办法，这可能会改变未来。
This might change in the future, if we
can figure out better ways of doing this.
但现在就在安全的这边我们要这么做
But just to be on the safe side right now,
that's what we're gonna do.
好的，让我们在这里开始使用一些数据。
Okay, so let's go ahead and
start using some data here.
所以在 App.js 中，抱歉，这不是 App.js，
So inside of App.js,
sorry, this isn't App.js,
这是 SearchParams.js的内部。
this is inside of SearchParams.js.
> > 布莱恩: 我们这里已经有动物了
&gt;&gt; Brian: We've already
got an animals here, but
我们也要把宠物客户弄上去
we're also going to get
the pet client up here.
> > 布莱恩: 在这些使用中的下拉菜单中，
&gt;&gt; Brian: And underneath all these
use dropdowns, and things like that,
我们要用 React 的另一个叫 " useEffect" 的东西
we're gonna use another thing
from React here called useEffect.
> > 布莱恩: 如果你熟悉雷法的话
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now,
if you're familiar with React, already,
useEffect 将取代几个生命周期挂钩，对吗 ?
useEffect is gonna take the place of
several of the lifecycle hooks, right?
所以它要取代 componentDidMount
So, it's gonna take the place
of componentDidMount,
componentWillUnmount 和 componentDidUpdate。
componentWillUnmount, and
componentDidUpdate.
所以如果你不知道这些是什么，那就好，你可以学习这些
So if you don't know what those are,
then that's fine, you can learn these for
第一次了
the first time.
但如果你很熟悉的话
But if you're coming in
with some familiarity,
这就是要取代的
that's what this is gonna replace.
所以我要说 " useEffect " ，然后我就给它一个功能。
So here I'm gonna say useEffect, and
then I'm gonna give it a function.
> > 布莱恩: 然后我就会说 pet.retends ，
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
then here I'm gonna say pet.breeds,
> > 布莱恩: 狗。
&gt;&gt; Brian: dog.
这会带来一个承诺
This is gonna return a promise.
你可以看到它回归了一个承诺。
You can actually see that
it returns a promise.
>> Brian: 返回一个品种响应。
&gt;&gt; Brian: That returns a breeds response.
然后就在这里我们可以看到它在做什么
And then here, just for now so
we can see what it's doing,
我要说 console.log 和 console.error。
I'm gonna say console.log and
console.error.
这句话是什么意思
And what this is saying,
如果呼叫成功，则无论响应是什么，记录输出。
if the call is successful then log
output whatever the response is,
如果不成功，则将其发送至 console.error。
and if it's not successful,
then send it to console.error.
> > 布莱恩: 这里发生了什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: So what's happening here?
因此，在呈现呈现时，将断开 useEffect 。
So useEffect is disconnected from
when the render is happening.
所以这实际上是在安排这个
So what this is actually doing
is this is scheduling this
在发生呈现之后运行。
function to run after the render happens.
接下来要发生的事是第一次
So what's gonna happen is it's
going to render the first time,
它将会安排使用效果来运行，但它会首先呈现。
it's going to schedule use effect to run,
but then it's going to render first.
所有这些东西都是在任何事情发生之前
So all of this stuff gets rendered
first before anything happens inside of
useEffect。
useEffect.
到目前为止还好吗
Good so far?
好吧这事不会马上发生的
All right, so
this does not happen immediately.
一旦发生这种情况，一旦搜索参数
As soon as this happens,
as soon as searchParams renders for
第一次，你就会有这种影响了，好吗 ?
the very first time,
t's then going to run this effect, okay?
而且它不像这样那样同步化，然后马上
And it's not synchronized its not like
this happens and then immediately
这种情况发生后不久，就会产生这种影响。
this happens, it happens and
then soon thereafter this effect will run.
你为什么要这么做
Now, why do you wanna do this?
你想这样做是因为你不想放慢第一次的速度
Well, you want to do this because you
don't wanna slow down that first render,
对吧 ?
right?
你想马上给你的用户展示点东西
You wanna show your users
something immediately.
你不想让他们等着看什么
You don't want them to have
to wait to see something,
您不希望它们等待某些类型的 Ajax 请求返回。
you don't want them to wait for
some sort of Ajax request to come back.
您要立即显示某些内容，然后转至 API 并尝试
You want to immediately show something and
then go to the API and try and
请求数据。
request data.
所以我们才这么做
So that's why we're doing this.
让我们来看看这看起来是什么样的。
So let's go take a look what
that actually looks like.
如果你去你的佩蒂那你应该看看这个对象
If you go over here into your petinder
you should see here this object breeds,
然后你就应该看到它现在有 257 种
breeds, and then you should see it
comes back right now with 257 breeds.
所以如果我看其中一个你可以看到哈斯基冰岛牧羊犬
So if I look at one of these you
can see Husky, Icelandic sheepdog.
我都不知道那是个品种但显然是吧
I didn't even know that was a breed,
but apparently it is, right?
因此，它从 API中返回了所有这些东西。
And so it comes back with all
these things back from the API.
如果你看看你的网络标签，你会发现这只是 JSX， XHR。
And if you look at your network tab
you'll see that this is just JSX, XHR.
这将会转至宠物 devs dev-apis ，并从 API 中获取。
This is going to the pet devs dev-apis,
and it is getting that back from the API.
> > 布莱恩: 这很棒，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Which is great, right?
现在我们从 API 中获取所有这些信息，所以现在我们实际上可以
Now we're getting all this information
back from the API, so now we can actually
它们都是各种不同种类的狗品种
setBreeds to be all of these various
different kinds of breeds of dogs.
>> 布莱恩: 我们要做的不是使用效果，而是替换这个
&gt;&gt; Brian: So what we're gonna do instead
of useEffect, we'll just replace this and
说> > 布莱恩: 我们想做的第一件事是
say,
&gt;&gt; Brian: The first thing we wanna do is,
每当此运行通过我们要更新的品种时，都将为空数组。
whenever this run through we want to
update breeds, to be empty array.
因为如果我们要申请新的品种并且已经有了新的品种
Because if we're requesting new breeds and
there's already breeds in that,
那我们就想把他们清理出来
then we want to clear them out.
我们要更新这个品种
We're gonna update the breed.
>> Brian: 要成为空字符串。
&gt;&gt; Brian: To be an empty string.
当我们改变品种的时候它就会开始运转
This useEffect, it's gonna get run
whenever we're changing sets of breeds,
对吧 ?
right?
所以如果我从猫到狗，我需要得到一套新的品种，对吗 ?
So if I go from like cats to dog,
I need to get a new set of breeds, right?
所以我要做的第一件事就是清除任何品种
So the first thing I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna clear out whatever breeds
都在里面
were in there.
所以如果有胡同和狮子狗的话我要把所有的东西都清理掉
So if there's husky and poodle, I'm
gonna clear all that stuff out of there.
如果我选 Bichon F起立或那样的话我就得
And if I've selected Bichon Frise or
something like that, then I need to
把它设置为空字符串，因为我不能有一个 Bichon F崛起猫。
set that to be empty string, as well,
because I can't have a Bichon Frise cat.
一旦完成了我就会说 pet.detd
So once that's done,
then I'm gonna say, pet.breeds,
这就是从 API中检索到的功能
which is that function that's
gonna retrieve that from the API.
我要去分析任何动物的情况
I'm gonna parse in whatever
animal is right there, so
动物 >> Brian: And
animal
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
然后我就会说， >> 布莱恩:
then I'm gonna say .then,
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
这会让我们从他们的 API 中回来
that's gonna give us something
back from their API, and
我知道这件物品里面会有品种
I know inside of that object
it's gonna have breeds.
> > 布莱恩: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay?
> > 布莱恩: 所以我们正在组织这个品种的卡兹我知道
&gt;&gt; Brian: So we're just structuring out
this breed cuz I know that's gonna come
从 API 返回。
back from the API.
然后我会说如果你看看这些物体
And then I'm gonna say,
if you look at these objects,
如果我们回到我们的控制台，注意它们是物体，对吧 ?
if we go back here to our console,
notice that they are objects, right?
所以叫福克斯 - 泰里耶和其他的东西对吧
So name, Fox Terrier, links,
something else, right?
我们只是想知道名字
We actually just want the names.
我们想把所有链接都扔掉，我们只需要名字。
We want to throw away all those links,
we just want the names.
因此，我们有一个对象列表，我们想将这些对象转换为字符串列表。
So we have a list of objects that we
wanna transform into a list of strings.
那么我们是如何做到的呢 ?
So how do we do that?
地图。
Map.
布莱恩: 我们要做的是，我们会说 const，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So what we're gonna do is,
we're gonna say const,
breedstrings = breeds.map ，我们将转至
breedstrings = breeds.map,
and we're gonna turn,
>> Brian: 名称。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Name into name.
> > 布莱恩: 在这里，我们会说， setBreeds 是 breedStrings。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then here, we're gonna
say setBreeds to be breedStrings.
> > 布莱恩: 怎么了 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: So what's going on with this?
我们只是把名字叫出来了对吧
Well, we just structured out the name,
right?
所以我们把它从那个里拿掉，然后我们就回去了，对吧 ?
So we grab poodle out of that and then
we would just return to poodle, right?
你也可能得花那么多时间
You also could have had
to spend like breed,
对象，然后是 breedObj.name，对吗 ?
object, and then be breedObj.name, right?
一样的
Same thing.
我觉得这个有点高雅。
I just think this is
a little bit more elegant.
>> 布莱恩: 好的，如果 API存在错误，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and just in case
there's an error from the API,
你就把 console.error 放在那儿
you just put console.error there.
所以它只会将错误的内容输入到 console.error中。
So it'll just feed whatever
the error is into console.error.
>> Brian: 这将与类似错误 console.error 错误相同，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: This would be the same as doing
like error, console.error error, right?
一样的
Same thing.
> > 布莱恩: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay.
> > 布莱恩: 是的，我有一套，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Yeah, I have these as set,
而不是更新 >> Brian: 因此
rather not update
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
改变这个不是那个
change this to be set, not that.